♪ ♪
♪ WAITING HERE
FOR SOMEONE ♪
♪ ONLY YESTERDAY
WE WERE ON THE RUN ♪
♪ YOU SMILED BACK AT ME AND
YOUR FACE LIT UP THE SUN ♪
♪ NOW I'M WAITING
HERE FOR SOMEONE ♪
♪ AND OH LOVE... ♪
♪ DO YOU FEEL THIS ROUGH ♪
♪ WHYS IT ONLY YOU
I'M THINKING OF ♪
♪ MY SHADOW'S DANCING WITHOUT
YOU FOR THE FIRST TIME ♪
♪ MY HEART IS HOPING, YOU'LL
WALK RIGHT IN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND TELL ME THERE ARE
THINGS THAT YOU REGRET, ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF I'M BEING HONEST
I AIN'T OVER YOU YET. ♪
♪ THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING,
IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK ♪
♪ ♪
♪ IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK ♪
♪ SOMEONE'S MOVING OUTSIDE ♪
♪ THE LIGHTS COME
ON DOWN THE DRIVE ♪
♪ I FORGET YOUR NOT HERE
WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ DO YOU TILL THINK
OF ME SOMETIMES ♪
♪ AND OH LOVE... ♪
♪ WATCH THE SUN COMING UP ♪
♪ DON'T IT FEEL FUCKED UP,
WE'RE NOT IN LOVE ♪
♪ MY SHADOW'S DANCING WITHOUT
YOU FOR THE FIRST TIME ♪
♪ MY HEART IS HOPING, YOU'LL
WALK RIGHT IN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND TELL ME THERE ARE
THINGS THAT YOU REGRET, ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF I'M BEING HONEST
I AIN'T OVER YOU YET. ♪
♪ THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING,
IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK ♪
♪ ♪
♪ MY SHADOW'S DANCING WITHOUT
YOU FOR THE FIRST TIME ♪
♪ MY HEART IS HOPING, YOU'LL
WALK RIGHT IN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND TELL ME THERE ARE
THINGS THAT YOU REGRET, ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF I'M BEING HONEST
I AIN'T OVER YOU YET. ♪
♪ MY SHADOW'S DANCING WITHOUT
YOU FOR THE FIRST TIME ♪
♪ MY HEART IS HOPING, YOU'LL
WALK RIGHT IN TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND TELL ME THERE ARE
THINGS THAT YOU REGRET, ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF I'M BEING HONEST
I AIN'T OVER YOU YET. ♪
♪ THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING,
IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK ♪